Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject file, 1899-1953; Series IV
  - Council"s Committee on Publications
    - Williams, W.W., undated (Box 289, Folder 261)
    - Winship, George P., 1926 (Box 289, Folder 261)
    - Winslow, C.E.A., 1918-1930 (Box 289, Folder 261)
    - Winternitz, Milton C., 1923-1930 (Box 289, Folder 261)
    - Wissler, Clark, 1929-1930 (Box 289, Folder 261)
    - Woodbine, George E., 1918-1928 (Box 289, Folder 262)
    - Woodruff, Lorande, 1921-1938 (Box 289, Folder 262)
    - Wooley, Edgar M., 1925 (Box 289, Folder 262)
    - Woolsey, Theodore S., 1918-1922 (Box 289, Folder 262)
    - Wright, Herbert, 1921 (Box 289, Folder 262)
    - Wyant, G.G., 1919-1920 (Box 289, Folder 263)
    - Yale, Elihu [books on], undated (Box 289, Folder 263)
    - Yerkes, Robert M., 1925-1927 (Box 289, Folder 263)
    - Young, Kare, 1921-1930 (Box 289, Folder 264)
    - Young, Kimball, undated (Box 289, Folder 264)
    - Yale University Press, 1917-1919 (Box 289, Folder 265)
    - Yale University Press, 1919-1936 (Box 289, Folder 266-268)
    - Yale University Press: History of, 1938 (Box 289, Folder 269)
  - Diplomas, 1902-1904 (Box 290, Folder 270-272)
  - Diplomas, 1916-1918 (Box 290, Folder 273-275)
  - Diplomas, 1920-1923 (Box 290, Folder 276-281)
  - Diplomas, 1924-1928 (Box 291, Folder 282-291)
  - Diplomas, 1929-1933 (Box 292, Folder 292-302)
  - Diplomas, 1933-1937 (Box 293, Folder 303-311)
  - Diplomas, 1937-1941 (Box 294, Folder 312-319)
  - Diplomas, 1941-1946 (Box 295, Folder 320-329)
  - Diplomas, 1945-1949 (Box 296, Folder 330-338)
  - Diplomas, 1948-1952 (Box 297, Folder 339-348)
  - Diplomas, 1952-1953 (Box 298, Folder 349-351)
  - Diplomas: Change of name, 1942-1952 (Box 298, Folder 352-354)
  - Diplomas, Committee on, 1923-1926 (Box 298, Folder 355)
  - Diplomas: Dorr, Harry B., 1941-1953 (Box 298, Folder 356-358)
  - Diplomas: duplicates, 1946-1953 (Box 299, Folder 359-363)
  - Engagement Books, 1913-1918 (Box 300, Folder 364-368)
  - Engagement Books, 1918-1924 (Box 301, Folder 369-374)
  - 1924-1930 (Box 302, Folder 375-380)
  - Engagement Books, 1930-1935 (Box 303, Folder 381-385)
    - Engineering: plans for development of 2 copies, 1920 May 6 (Box 304, Folder 386)
    - Engineering: importance of developing copy 1, n. d. (Box 304, Folder 387)
    - Engineering: importance of developing copy 2, undated (Box 304, Folder 388)
    - Engineering: importance of developing [supplement], undated (Box 304, Folder 389)
  - Honorary Degrees
    - General
      - A-D, 1922 (Box 305, Folder 390)
      - E-L, 1922 (Box 305, Folder 391)
      - M-Z, 1922 (Box 305, Folder 392)
    - Letters of Comment from Corporation Members, 1922 (Box 305, Folder 393)
    - Lists, 1922 (Box 305, Folder 394)
    - Miscellaneous, 1922 (Box 305, Folder 395)
    - General, 1923 (Box 305, Folder 396)
      - A-D, 1923 (Box 305, Folder 397)
      - E-L, 1923 (Box 305, Folder 398)
      - M-R, 1923 (Box 306, Folder 399)
      - S-Z, 1923 (Box 306, Folder 400)
    - General, 1924 (Box 306, Folder 401)
      - A-B, 1924 (Box 306, Folder 402)
      - C-G, 1924 (Box 306, Folder 403)
      - H-J, 1924 (Box 306, Folder 404)
      - K-M, 1924 (Box 306, Folder 405)
      - O-S, 1924 (Box 306, Folder 406)
      - T-Z, 1924 (Box 306, Folder 407)
    - General, 1925 (Box 306, Folder 408)
      - A-C, 1925 (Box 306, Folder 409)
      - D-G, 1925 (Box 306, Folder 410)
      - H-J, 1925 (Box 307, Folder 411)
      - K-M, 1925 (Box 307, Folder 412)
      - N-Q, 1925 (Box 307, Folder 413)
      - R-Z, 1925 (Box 307, Folder 414)
    - General, 1926 (Box 307, Folder 415-416)
      - A-B, 1926 (Box 307, Folder 417)
      - C-D, 1926 (Box 307, Folder 418)
      - E-J, 1926 (Box 307, Folder 419)
      - K-M, 1926 (Box 307, Folder 420)
      - N-S, 1926 (Box 307, Folder 421)
      - T-Z, 1926 (Box 307, Folder 422)
    - General, 1927 (Box 308, Folder 423-424)
      - A-G, 1927 (Box 308, Folder 425)
      - H-I, 1927 (Box 308, Folder 426)
      - J-K, 1927 (Box 308, Folder 427)
      - L-M, 1927 (Box 308, Folder 428)
      - N-S, 1927 (Box 308, Folder 429)
      - T-Z, 1927 (Box 308, Folder 430)
    - General, 1928 (Box 308, Folder 431-432)
      - A-B, 1928 (Box 308, Folder 433)
      - C-F, 1928 (Box 308, Folder 434)
      - G-I, 1928 (Box 309, Folder 435)
      - J-R, 1928 (Box 309, Folder 436)
      - S-Z, 1928 (Box 309, Folder 437)
    - General, 1929 (Box 309, Folder 438-439)
      - A-B, 1929 (Box 309, Folder 440)
      - C-D, 1929 (Box 309, Folder 441)
      - E-G, 1929 (Box 309, Folder 442)
      - H, 1929 (Box 309, Folder 443)
      - I-L, 1929 (Box 309, Folder 444)
      - M, 1929 (Box 309, Folder 445)
      - N-R, 1929 (Box 309, Folder 446)
      - S, 1929 (Box 310, Folder 447)
      - S, 1929 (Box 310, Folder 448)
      - T-Z, 1929 (Box 310, Folder 449)
    - General, 1930 (Box 310, Folder 450-451)
      - A-B, 1930 (Box 310, Folder 452)
      - C-F, 1930 (Box 310, Folder 453)
      - G-H, 1930 (Box 310, Folder 454)
      - I-L, 1930 (Box 310, Folder 455)
      - M, 1930 (Box 310, Folder 456)
      - N-Z, 1930 (Box 310, Folder 457)
    - General, 1931 (Box 311, Folder 458)
      - A- C, 1931 (Box 311, Folder 459)
      - D-G, 1931 (Box 312, Folder 460)
      - H-M, 1931 (Box 312, Folder 461)
      - N-Q, 1931 (Box 312, Folder 462)
      - R, 1931 (Box 312, Folder 463)
      - S-Z, 1931 (Box 312, Folder 464)
    - General, 1932 (Box 312, Folder 465)
      - A-B, 1932 (Box 312, Folder 466)
      - C-G, 1932 (Box 312, Folder 467)
      - H-M, 1932 (Box 312, Folder 468)
      - N-O, 1932 (Box 312, Folder 469)
      - P-Z, 1932 (Box 312, Folder 470)
    - General, 1933 (Box 312, Folder 471)
      - A-B, 1933 (Box 312, Folder 472)
      - C-D, 1933 (Box 312, Folder 473)
      - E-J, 1933 (Box 312, Folder 474)
      - K-M, 1933 (Box 312, Folder 475)
      - N-R, 1933 (Box 312, Folder 476)
      - S-Z, 1933 (Box 312, Folder 477)
    - General, 1934 (Box 312, Folder 478)
      - A-C, 1934 (Box 312, Folder 479)
      - D-F, 1934 (Box 312, Folder 480)
      - G, 1934 (Box 312, Folder 481)
      - H-K, 1934 (Box 312, Folder 482)
      - L-R, 1934 (Box 313, Folder 483)
      - S, 1934 (Box 313, Folder 484)
      - T-Z, 1934 (Box 313, Folder 485)
    - General, 1935 (Box 314, Folder 486)
      - A-B, 1935 (Box 313, Folder 487)
      - C-F, 1935 (Box 313, Folder 488)
      - G-J, 1935 (Box 313, Folder 489)
      - K-L, 1935 (Box 313, Folder 490)
      - M-N, 1935 (Box 313, Folder 491)
      - O-R, 1935 (Box 313, Folder 492)
      - S, 1935 (Box 313, Folder 493)
      - T-Z, 1935 (Box 313, Folder 494)
    - General, 1936 (Box 314, Folder 495)
      - A-C, 1936 (Box 314, Folder 496)
      - D-G, 1936 (Box 314, Folder 497)
      - H-L, 1936 (Box 315, Folder 498)
      - M, 1936 (Box 316, Folder 499)
      - N-S, 1936 (Box 316, Folder 500)
      - T-Z, 1936 (Box 316, Folder 501)
    - General, 1937 (Box 317, Folder 502)
      - A-D, 1937 (Box 317, Folder 503)
      - E-G, 1937 (Box 317, Folder 504)
      - H, 1937 (Box 315, Folder 505)
      - J-L, 1937 (Box 315, Folder 506)
      - M-P, 1937 (Box 315, Folder 507)
      - Q-S, 1937 (Box 315, Folder 508)
      - T-Z, 1937 (Box 315, Folder 509)
    - General, 1938 (Box 315, Folder 510)
      - A-C, 1938 (Box 315, Folder 511)
      - D-G, 1938 (Box 315, Folder 512)
      - H, 1938 (Box 315, Folder 513)
      - I-L, 1938 (Box 315, Folder 514)
      - M, 1938 (Box 315, Folder 515)
      - N-R, 1938 (Box 316, Folder 516)
      - S-Z, 1938 (Box 316, Folder 517)
    - General, 1939 (Box 316, Folder 518)
      - A-B, 1939 (Box 316, Folder 519)
      - C-E, 1939 (Box 316, Folder 520)
      - F-G, 1939 (Box 316, Folder 521)
      - H-J, 1939 (Box 316, Folder 522)
      - K-M, 1939 (Box 316, Folder 523)
      - N-S, 1939 (Box 316, Folder 524)
      - T-Z, 1939 (Box 316, Folder 525)
    - General, 1940 (Box 317, Folder 526)
      - A, 1940 (Box 317, Folder 527)
      - B, 1940 (Box 317, Folder 528)
      - C, 1940 (Box 317, Folder 529)
      - D-G, 1940 (Box 317, Folder 530)
      - H, 1940 (Box 317, Folder 531)
      - I-K, 1940 (Box 317, Folder 532)
      - L-R, 1940 (Box 317, Folder 533)
      - S, 1940 (Box 317, Folder 534)
      - T-Z, 1940 (Box 317, Folder 535)
    - General, 1941 (Box 318, Folder 536)
      - A-B, 1941 (Box 318, Folder 537)
      - C-G, 1941 (Box 318, Folder 538)
      - H-J, 1941 (Box 318, Folder 539)
      - K-R, 1941 (Box 318, Folder 540)
      - S, 1941 (Box 318, Folder 541)
      - T-Z, 1941 (Box 318, Folder 542)
    - General, 1942 (Box 319, Folder 543)
      - A-B, 1942 (Box 319, Folder 544)
      - C, 1942 (Box 319, Folder 545)
      - D-F, 1942 (Box 319, Folder 546)
      - G-H, 1942 (Box 319, Folder 547)
      - I-L, 1942 (Box 319, Folder 548)
      - M, 1942 (Box 319, Folder 549)
      - N-R, 1942 (Box 319, Folder 550)
      - S, 1942 (Box 319, Folder 551)
      - T-Z, 1942 (Box 319, Folder 552)
    - General, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 553)
      - A-B, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 554)
      - C-F, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 555)
      - G-J, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 556)
      - K-M, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 557)
      - N-Q, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 558)
      - R, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 559)
      - S-Z, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 560)
    - General, 1947 (Box 320, Folder 561-562)
      - A-B, 1947 (Box 320, Folder 563)
      - C-G, 1947 (Box 320, Folder 564)
      - H-O, 1947 (Box 320, Folder 565)
      - P-Z, 1947 (Box 320, Folder 566)
    - General, 1948 (Box 320, Folder 567)
      - A-B, 1948 (Box 320, Folder 568)
      - C-D, 1948 (Box 320, Folder 569)
      - E-J, 1948 (Box 320, Folder 570)
      - K-O, 1948 (Box 320, Folder 571)
      - P-Z, 1948 (Box 320, Folder 572)
    - General, 1949 (Box 321, Folder 573)
      - A-C, 1949 (Box 321, Folder 574)
      - D, 1949 (Box 321, Folder 575)
      - E-J, 1949 (Box 321, Folder 576)
      - K-O, 1949 (Box 321, Folder 577)
      - P-R, 1949 (Box 321, Folder 578)
      - S-Z, 1949 (Box 321, Folder 579)
    - General, 1950 (Box 321, Folder 580)
      - A-C, 1950 (Box 321, Folder 581)
      - D-G, 1950 (Box 321, Folder 582)
      - H-J, 1950 (Box 321, Folder 583)
      - K-L, 1950 (Box 321, Folder 584)
      - M-Q, 1950 (Box 321, Folder 585)
      - R, 1950 (Box 322, Folder 586)
      - S, 1950 (Box 322, Folder 587)
      - T-Z, 1950 (Box 322, Folder 588)
    - General, 1951 (Box 322, Folder 589-590)
      - A-B, 1951 (Box 322, Folder 591)
      - C-F, 1951 (Box 322, Folder 592)
      - G, 1951 (Box 322, Folder 593)
      - H-M, 1951 (Box 322, Folder 594)
      - N-R, 1951 (Box 322, Folder 595)
      - S, 1951 (Box 322, Folder 596)
      - T, 1951 (Box 322, Folder 597)
      - U-Z, 1951 (Box 322, Folder 598)
    - General, 1952 (Box 323, Folder 599)
      - A-L, 1952 (Box 323, Folder 600)
      - M-Z, 1952 (Box 323, Folder 601)
    - General, 1953 (Box 323, Folder 602)
      - A-C, 1953 (Box 323, Folder 603)
      - D-F, 1953 (Box 323, Folder 604)
      - G-J, 1953 (Box 323, Folder 605)
      - K-M, 1953 (Box 323, Folder 606)
      - N-Z, 1953 (Box 323, Folder 607)
  - Inauguration Committee: minutes of meetings, 1921 (Box 324, Folder 608)
  - Inauguration Correspondence, 1921
    - A-C, 1921 (Box 324, Folder 609)
    - D-G, 1921 (Box 324, Folder 610)
    - H-L, 1921 (Box 324, Folder 611)
    - M-P, 1921 (Box 324, Folder 612)
    - Q-T, 1921 (Box 324, Folder 613)
    - U, 1921 (Box 324, Folder 614-615)
    - V-Z, 1921 (Box 324, Folder 616)
    - Alumni Luncheon (Box 324, Folder 617)
    - City and State officials (Box 324, Folder 618)
    - General (Box 324, Folder 619)
    - German Universities (Box 325, Folder 620)
    - Learned Societies (Box 325, Folder 621)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 325, Folder 622)
    - President Hadley"s reception (Box 325, Folder 623)
    - Public and Preparatory schools Inauguration (Box 325, Folder 624)
  - Inauguration
    - Dinner, 1921 (Box 325, Folder 625)
    - Entertainment, 1921 (Box 325, Folder 626)
    - Faculty dinner, 1921 (Box 325, Folder 627)
    - Form letters, 1921 (Box 325, Folder 628)
    - Form sent out, 1921 (Box 325, Folder 629)
    - Memorabilia, 1921 (Box 325, Folder 630)
    - Memorial Quadrangle room assignments, 1921 (Box 325, Folder 631)
    - Official record of, 1921 (Box 325, Folder 632)
    - Platform guests, 1921 (Box 325, Folder 633)
    - Program copy, 1921 (Box 325, Folder 634)
    - Tickets, 1921 (Box 325, Folder 635)
  - Institute of International Studies
    - International relations, 1933-1937 (Box 326, Folder 636)
    - Research in International relations, 1934 (Box 326, Folder 637)
    - Research in International relations supplement, undated (Box 326, Folder 638)
    - Report of the executive committee, [1941?] (Box 326, Folder 639)
    - Program for the second five year period, 1941-1946 (Box 326, Folder 640)
    - Spykman, Nicholas J., "International Relations", undated (Box 326, Folder 641)
  - President"s Committee on University Development
    - An Introduction to Yale, 1939 (Box 327, Folder 642)
    - Automatic engineering and internal combustion, 1940 (Box 327, Folder 643)
    - Chemical engineering, proposal for development in, 1941 (Box 327, Folder 644)
    - Engineering at Yale, 1940 (Box 327, Folder 645)
    - "Engineers for Tomorrow", 1940 (Box 327, Folder 646)
    - Engineering, why the school needs additional funds, 1940 (Box 327, Folder 647)
    - Gibbs, J. Willard, the works of, 1939 (Box 327, Folder 648)
    - Law Library Fund, 1939, undated (Box 327, Folder 649)
    - Law Library, plan for development in criminal law and legal medicine, 1940 (Box 327, Folder 650)
    - Legal research, memorandum on proposed institute of, undated (Box 327, Folder 651)
    - Medical Library, 1940 (Box 327, Folder 652)
    - School of Medicine, dental clinic and training unit, 1939 (Box 327, Folder 653)
    - Doctors for America, 1939 (Box 327, Folder 654)
    - School of Medicine, haemolytic streptococci, research on, 1939 (Box 327, Folder 655)
    - School of Medicine, Plan for an Attack on Deafness, 1940 (Box 327, Folder 656)
    - Metallurgy, opportunities and needs in, 1940 (Box 327, Folder 657)
    - Metallurgy, proposal for increase of Guggunheim Fund for, 1940 (Box 327, Folder 658)
    - New Haven Hospital and Dispensary, 1940 (Box 327, Folder 659)
    - Nutrition, Proposal for an institute of, 1940 (Box 327, Folder 660)
    - "Psychiatry at Yale", 1940 (Box 327, Folder 661)
    - Public health, opportunities and needs, 1939, 1940 (Box 327, Folder 662)
    - "Yale in Publication", undated (Box 327, Folder 663)
  - Press Releases, 1911-1917 (Box 328, Folder 664-669)
  - Receipted Bills
    - A, 1927-1938 (Box 329, Folder 670)
    - B, 1925-1935 (Box 329, Folder 671)
    - B, 1926-1934 (Box 329, Folder 672)
    - B, 1931-1934 (Box 329, Folder 673)
    - B, 1936-1938 (Box 329, Folder 674)
    - C, 1926-1934 (Box 329, Folder 675)
    - C, 1931-1938 (Box 329, Folder 676)
    - D, 1927-1934 (Box 329, Folder 677)
    - E, 1928-1934 (Box 330, Folder 678)
    - F, 1927-1932 (Box 330, Folder 679)
    - G, 1927-1934 (Box 330, Folder 680)
    - H, 1926-1934 (Box 330, Folder 681)
    - J, 1927-1934 (Box 330, Folder 682)
    - K, 1925-1932 (Box 330, Folder 683)
    - L, 1925-1934 (Box 330, Folder 684)
    - M, 1927-1933 (Box 330, Folder 685)
    - N, 1927-1940 (Box 330, Folder 686)
    - N, 1932-1935 (Box 330, Folder 687)
    - O, 1926-1933 (Box 331, Folder 688)
    - P, 1925-1934 (Box 331, Folder 689)
    - Q, 1930 (Box 331, Folder 690)
    - R, 1926-1935 (Box 331, Folder 691)
    - S, 1925-1930 (Box 331, Folder 692)
    - S, 1932-1940 (Box 331, Folder 693)
    - T, 1926-1934 (Box 331, Folder 694)
    - U, 1927-1935 (Box 331, Folder 695)
    - V, 1926-1929 (Box 331, Folder 696)
    - W, 1929-1941 (Box 331, Folder 697)
    - X-Y-Z, 1925-1941 (Box 331, Folder 698)
    - Yale (Box 332, Folder 699-700)
  - Reorganization of the University
    - 1918 December 12 (Box 333, Folder 701)
    - Corporation statement, 1918 December 17 (Box 333, Folder 702)
    - Statements, 1919 January 20 (Box 333, Folder 703)
    - 1919 March 6 (Box 333, Folder 704)
    - Report of the educational committee, 1919 March 11 (Box 333, Folder 705)
    - Notes and drafts, Circa 1919 (Box 333, Folder 706)
    - Printed material, 1919 (Box 333, Folder 707)
  - Reports to the President
    - 1929-1930 Admissions-English (Box 334, Folder 708)
    - 1929-1930 French-Observatory (Box 334, Folder 709)
    - 1929-1930 Personnel-Zoology (Box 334, Folder 710)
    - 1930-1931 Bacteriology-Divinity (Box 334, Folder 711)
    - 1930-1931 Engineering-English (Box 334, Folder 712)
    - 1930-1931 Geology-Peabody Museum (Box 335, Folder 713)
    - 1930-1931 Personal Study-Zoology (Box 335, Folder 714)
    - 1931-1932 Admissions-Electrical Engineering (Box 335, Folder 715)
    - 1931-1932 Engineering Mechanics-Mining (Box 335, Folder 716)
    - 1931-1932 Natural Preserve-Physiological Chemistry (Box 335, Folder 717)
    - 1931-1932 Physiology-Zoology (Box 335, Folder 718)
    - 1932-1933 Chaplain-English (Box 336, Folder 719)
    - 1932-1933 Forestry-Pharmacology (Box 336, Folder 720)
    - 1932-1933 Philosophy-Zoology (Box 336, Folder 721)
    - 1933-1934 Admissions-Chemistry (Box 336, Folder 722)
    - 1933-1934 Child Development-Forestry (Box 336, Folder 723)
    - 1933-1934 French-Law (Box 336, Folder 724)
    - 1933-1934 Library-Observatory (Box 336, Folder 725)
    - 1933-1934 Payne Whitney-Physiology (Box 337, Folder 726)
    - 1933-1934 Psychology-Zoology (Box 337, Folder 727)
    - 1934-1935 Athletics-Engineering (Box 337, Folder 728)
    - 1934-1935 French-Physics (Box 337, Folder 729)
    - 1934-1935 Physiology (Box 337, Folder 730)
    - 1934-1935 Psychology-Zoology (Box 338, Folder 731)
    - 1935-1936 Anatomy-Education (Box 337, Folder 732)
    - 1935-1936 Engineering-Oriental Studies (Box 338, Folder 733)
    - 1935-1936 Pharmacology-Zoology (Box 338, Folder 734)
    - 1935-1936 college reports (Box 338, Folder 735)
    - 1935-1936 miscellaneous papers (Box 338, Folder 736)
    - 1936-1937 Anatomy-Classics (Box 338, Folder 737)
    - 1936-1937 Economics-Military Science (Box 338, Folder 738)
    - 1936-1937 Naval Science-Zoology (Box 338, Folder 739)
    - 1937-1938 Anatomy-Classics (Box 339, Folder 740)
    - 1937-1938 Civil Engineering-Metallurgy (Box 339, Folder 741)
    - 1937-1938 Military Science-Zoology (Box 339, Folder 742)
    - 1938-1939 Anatomy-Economics (Box 339, Folder 743)
    - 1938-1939 Education-Philosophy (Box 339, Folder 744)
    - 1938-1939 Physical Education (Box 339, Folder 745)
    - 1938-1939 Physics-Zoology (Box 339, Folder 746)
    - 1939-1940 Anatomy-Education (Box 340, Folder 747)
    - 1939-1940 Electrical Engineering-Physics (Box 340, Folder 748)
    - 1939-1940 Physiology-Zoology (Box 340, Folder 749)
    - 1940-1941 Anatomy-Electrical Engineering (Box 340, Folder 750)
    - 1940-1941 English-Pharmacology (Box 340, Folder 751)
    - 1940-1941 Philosophy-Zoology (Box 340, Folder 752)
    - 1941-1942 Anatomy-Education (Box 341, Folder 753)
    - 1941-1942 English-Naval Science (Box 341, Folder 754)
    - 1941-1942 Neuroanatomy-Spanish and Italian (Box 341, Folder 755)
    - 1942-1943 Anatomy-English (Box 341, Folder 756)
    - 1942-1943 French-Physics (Box 341, Folder 757)
    - 1942-1943 Physiological Chemistry-Zoology (Box 341, Folder 758)
    - 1942-1943 Master"s reports (Box 341, Folder 759)
    - 1943-1944 Anatomy-Education (Box 342, Folder 760)
    - 1943-1944 Electrical Engineering-Pharmacology (Box 342, Folder 761)
    - 1943-1944 Philosophy-Zoology (Box 342, Folder 762)
    - 1943-1944 Master"s reports (Box 342, Folder 763)
    - 1944-1945 Anatomy-Economics (Box 342, Folder 764)
    - 1944-1945 Electrical Engineering-Mathematics (Box 342, Folder 765)
    - 1944-1945 Mechanical Engineering-Pharmacology (Box 342, Folder 766)
    - 1944-1945 Philosophy-Zoology (Box 342, Folder 767)
    - 1945-1946 Anatomy-Electrical Engineering (Box 343, Folder 768)
    - 1945-1946 English-Oriental Studies (Box 343, Folder 769)
    - 1945-1946 Pharmacology-Physics (Box 343, Folder 770)
    - 1945-1946 Physiological Chemistry-Zoology (Box 343, Folder 771)
    - 1946-1947 Anatomy-Education (Box 343, Folder 772)
    - 1946-1947 Electrical Engineering-Mechanical Engineering (Box 343, Folder 773)
    - 1946-1947 Metallurgy-Physics (Box 343, Folder 774)
    - 1946-1947 Physiological Chemistry-Zoology (Box 343, Folder 775)
    - 1947-1948 Anatomy-Classics (Box 344, Folder 776)
    - 1947-1948 Economics-Music (Box 344, Folder 777)
    - 1947-1948 Naval Science-Physiological Chemistry (Box 344, Folder 778)
    - 1947-1948 Physiology-Zoology (Box 344, Folder 779)
    - 1948-1949 American Studies-Electrical Engineering (Box 344, Folder 780)
    - 1948-1949 English-Painting (Box 344, Folder 781)
    - 1948-1949 Pharmacology-Physiology (Box 344, Folder 782)
    - 1948-1949 Physiological Chemistry-Zoology (Box 344, Folder 783)
    - 1949-1950 American Studies-Civil Engineering (Box 345, Folder 784)
    - 1949-1950 Drama-Oriental Studies (Box 345, Folder 785)
    - 1949-1950 Naval Science-Plant Science (Box 345, Folder 786)
    - 1949-1950 Political Science-Zoology (Box 345, Folder 788)
    - 1950-1951 Air Science-Engineering (Box 345, Folder 789)
    - 1950-1951 French-History (Box 345, Folder 790)
    - 1950-1951 History of Art-Near Eastern Languages and Literature (Box 346, Folder 791)
    - 1950-1951 Pharmacology-Political Science (Box 346, Folder 792)
    - 1950-1951 Psychiatric Social Service-Psychology (Box 346, Folder 793)
    - 1950-1951 Public Health-Sociology (Box 346, Folder 794)
    - 1951-1952 Air Science-Civil Engineering (Box 346, Folder 795)
    - 1951-1952 Classics-Economics (Box 346, Folder 796)
    - 1951-1952 Education-Mathematics (Box 347, Folder 797)
    - 1951-1952 Mechanical Engineering-Pathology (Box 347, Folder 798)
    - 1951-1952 Pediatrics-Physics (Box 347, Folder 799)
    - 1951-1952 Public Health (Box 347, Folder 800)
    - 1951-1952 Service Bureau-Zoology (Box 347, Folder 801)
    - 1952-1953 Air Science-Chemistry (Box 347, Folder 802)
    - 1952-1953 Child Study Center-History (Box 347, Folder 803)
    - 1952-1953 History of Art-Near Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 348, Folder 804)
    - 1952-1953 Obstetrics and Gynecology-Physical Education (Box 348, Folder 805)
    - 1952-1953 Physics-Psychology (Box 348, Folder 806)
    - 1952-1953 Public Health (Box 348, Folder 807)
    - 1952-1953 Slavic Languages-Zoology (Box 348, Folder 808)
    - 1952-1953 Masters' reports (Box 348, Folder 809)
  - Revision of Yale and New Haven
    - Correspondence, statistics, and related material, 1933 (Box 349, Folder 810-816)
    - Correspondence, statistics, and related material, 1936-1937 (Box 350, Folder 817-820)
    - Letters of inquiry concerning Revolutionary War records of Yale graduates, 1929 (Box 351, Folder 821)
    - Typed copies of Revolutionary War records of Yale graduates (Box 351, Folder 822-824)
  - Two Hundred & Fiftieth Anniversary
    See: YRG 4-A-12 acc 12/51
  - Vocational Guidance, Personnel Analysis, Mental and Nervous Diseases
    - Antioch College, 1923-1924 (Box 352, Folder 825)
    - Brown University, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 826)
    - Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 827)
    - Cincinnati University, 1923-1924 (Box 352, Folder 827)
    - Columbia University, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 827)
    - Dartmouth College, 1923-1924 (1923) (Box 352, Folder 828)
    - Goucher College, 1923-1924 (Box 352, Folder 829)
    - Harvard University, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 829)
    - Illinois University, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 829)
    - Iowa University, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 829)
    - Michigan University, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 830)
    - Middlebury College, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 830)
    - Minnesota University, 1923-1924 (Box 352, Folder 830)
    - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 831)